This is the last thing I'm going to say before I go to bed. I'm trying to understand how so many
of you who have never protested, who have never studied protests, who know virtually nothing
about resistance, about movements, like all you know is maybe Martin Luther King.
I'm trying to understand why so many of you all are so confident in questioning things.
That are being told to you by people who have done all the above and I don't mean questioning
for clarity or for information seeking. I mean doubt. I don't. It is a part of the American
exceptionalism. That's really what it is but I will just I want to say this to you. For many of you
this time that we're in is the first time that you're realizing that it could be a time.
So it would behoove you to do less talking and more listening and learning to those who have
been recognizing not only that the time was coming but who have studied what has happened
during other times. So let's remove the ego and engage the curiosity.
curiosity.